(Penny:)Let's just
take the test.
(Leonard:)No, no, no,
I don't want to.
(Penny:)Oh, well, 'cause you
know we're gonna do bad.
(Leonard:)Because it doesn't matter.
(Sheldon:)I don't care
if we're a ten or a two.
(Sheldon:)Or a one.
A one is possible.
(Leonard:)Marriage is scary.
(Leonard:)You're scared, I'm scared.
(Leonard:)But it doesn't make me
not want to do it.
It-it just...
(Leonard:)makes me want to hold your hand
and do it with you.
(Howard:)Leonard...
(Amy:)It would make me so happy
if you said things like that.
(Sheldon:)We got an
eight-point-two.
(Sheldon:)Trust me, you're happy.
Mm! I love how they put
a waterfall at center field.
(Raj:)It really ties
the whole stadium together.
(Penny:)Look at you, talking sports.